# SAM PROWSE

(609) 848-3748 SPROWSEART@GMAIL.COM

WEB DESIGNER & DEVELOPER UNION CITY, NJ

Hey, I'm Sam! I'm a lifelong learner who has been working in web and graphic design for the past 10 years. I love working in an environment where there's always a new problem to solve. I'm passionate about doing my best work and helping my team create great things.



### **EXPERIENCE**

## WEB & GRAPHIC DESIGNER | Tabrasa, LLC October 2014 - Present

At Tabrasa, I've been responsible for managing, designing, and developing our CMS library of email and print marketing content for real estate agents and mortgage loan officers. I've also designed and built website templates, landing pages, and open house flyers for our client companies.

# **WEB CONTENT MANAGER** | The College of New Jersey May 2013 - March 2014

As a web content manager, I was responsible for building and updating the sites for TCNJ's academic departments using Wordpress. I gained experience with HTML, CSS, Javascript, and PHP. I also designed various infographics and banners, and edited the photography used on the sites.

# **WEB DEVELOPMENT INTERN** | The Green Economy September 2013 - January 2014

In this position, I worked to design and build a new website for The Green Economy, an online magazine, using the Wordpress CMS.. I gained experience with creating Wordpress themes from scratch using HTML, CSS, and PHP.

#### **PORTFOLIO:**

sprowse-dev.github.io

### **SKILLS**

#### Coding

HTML, CSS, Javascript, PHP, Wordpress CMS

# Wireframes & Mockups

Figma, Sketch, Photoshop

#### **Adobe Suite**

Photoshop, InDesign, Illustrator, Premiere, AfterEffects

#### **General Skills**

Email and Print Design, Mobile Responsive Email, Infographics, Illustration, Photo and Video Editing

#### Microsoft Suite

Powerpoint, Word, Excel, Outlook

### **EDUCATION**

2009-2013 B.F.A Digital Art and Minor in Computer Science The College of New Jersey